verotel.com 2019-10-31

# Verotel Never Missed a Payment

## About Verotel

Verotel is a leading Internet Payment Service Provider (IPSP) that has been enabling more than 50,000 high-risk webmasters with building their online businesses since 1998. Verotel understands the risks involved in supplying digital content and provides a PCI compliant solution. 

Verotel is the first high risk IPSP awarded with the official Payment Institute status. Processing all major credit cards and offering a fully PCI compliant solution, Verotel is the most trusted online payment processor in the business. Verotel's suite of online billing solutions is perfect for online businesses of any size. Our account offerings are specifically tailored to all payment processing needs: from the sole proprietor with a small website to larger merchants with a portfolio of online properties.

#### Company History

  * 1998 \- Verotel processed its first transaction on January 15th 1998
  * 2005 \- PCI was introduced. Verotel became PCI DSS Compliant
  * 2011 \- Verotel was licensed as Payment Institute by Dutch Central Bank
  * 2012 \- Verotel became Payment Facilitator with MasterCard and VISA
  * 2016 \- Verotel launches VR partnerships

## Verotel Payment Options

Verotel accepts a wide range of payments options at competitive rates. Verotel puts you in control, allowing you to decide which payment options you prefer to offer to your customer. 

You can make a decision with one click of a button and no additional software is needed to add a payment option. Verotel does all the work, while you simply watch your customer base and revenues increase.

Verotel allows you to accept payments in a range of currencies, including USD, CAD, AUD, EUR, GBP, NOK, DKK, SEK and CHF. You can receive your merchant revenues in USD, EUR or GBP. 

## Flexible billing options

Traditionally, online entertainment is billed on a subscription basis. Subscriptions are created when a subscriber clicks a Buy Now or Join Now button and submits their information for approval. Verotel offers a Remote User Manager tool for adding, modifying and deleting subscribers instantly.

Next to a Buy Now or Join Now button, Verotel offers FlexPay. Flexpay allows Verotel merchants to send any amount and any description directly to Verotel's order pages. Verotel FlexPay allows Verotel merchants to charge for content, with or without the need for a innovative way of billing is the perfect solution for cam sites and other token-based systems to sell pre-paid credit.  

View our plans

## Make More Money With More Traffic

To increase sales, more traffic is key. Verotel OpenAffiliate is a simple way of generating more traffic and increasing revenue by having other websites advertise your services or content. **Verotel's Affiliate system is used by tens of thousands affiliates/resellers around the world**.

Affiliates that have already a Verotel ID can with one click add your campaign to their traffic inventory. Verotel OpenAffiliate supports flexible landing pages, video and image galleries and a lot more. Verotel OpenAffiliate will increase traffic and increase sales!

## Security Policy

**Customers that purchase content through Verotel's webmasters and merchants can be assured that their information is handled in a completely confidential manner.**

#### Storage of transactions and credit card data

All data on Verotel's premises are stored and protected by state-of-the-art security systems. Our network facilities are monitored 24 hours, 7 days per week, for any downtime, intrusion or attack. All network facilities are physically protected by biometric access control systems. Verotel is fully compliant with the MasterCard Site Data Protection program and VISA Account Information Security program.

#### Filling in your credit card information

All transactions are only accepted on pages encrypted with SSL technology. SSL (Secure Socket Layer) makes it possible to encrypt all data on the browser side, and to decrypt the information when it reaches Verotel's servers. This way no one on the Internet can read the data (including your credit card information) completely protecting your privacy.

#### New transactions

All new transactions are fully screened by the Verotel Veronica anti-fraud system. Verotel Veronica verifies and cross-references the information supplied to Verotel. It combines information and checks this with data from more than 200 sources. Because of this intensive anti-fraud verification system, costs of fraudulent transactions and chargebacks are substantially reduced.

At Verotel, we are committed to protect the privacy of both merchants and cardholders. We use the information we collect about cardholders and payment information to process transactions only. Private account and address information is necessary to verify that you are the person making the purchase and to thwart potential fraud. All information gathered in the course of a transaction is transmitted securely and is protected by our database throughout the transaction process.

**WE WILL NEVER PROVIDE YOUR INFORMATION TO ANOTHER PARTY AND WE WILL NEVER SOLICIT YOU.**

#### What information do we collect? How do we use it?

When you order as a cardholder, we need to know your name, e-mail address, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, credit card, debit card, or checking account number, CVC code and expiration date. Sometimes we require your mailing address as well. This information allows us to safely process your transaction. We log the IP address for address verification and risk management purposes.

**WE ONLY USE THE INFORMATION TO PROCESS, CONFIRM AND NOTIFY YOU OF THE SPECIFIC TRANSACTION YOU ARE MAKING.**

#### How does Verotel protect customer information?

When you place orders or access your account information, we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

#### What about "cookies"?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide features such as linking and reselling. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that.

Verotel.com contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are clicking to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

**WE WILL NOT INCLUDE PERSONAL IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.**

Verotel may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to  
> Comply with law,  
> Enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or  
> Protect the rights, property or safety of Verotel, our users, or others. 

In summary: We are committed to protect your privacy. We use the information we collect on the order page to process orders and protect you against unauthorized transactions. We do not sell,trade, or rent your personal information to others. Your consent: By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Verotel. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**WE NEVER PROVIDE PERSONAL CREDIT CARD, DEBIT CARD OR BANDING INFORMATION WITH ANY REGISTERED SELLER.**

#### How will Verotel correspond with me?

Verotel will notify cardholders by email that their transaction was completed (receipt). 

Verotel is an Internet Payment Service Provider based in Amsterdam.

Danzigerkade 23D  
1013 AP   Amsterdam  
Netherlands
